I'm in love with you and
I don't care who knows it!
Dreams do come true, my friends.
I've been reincarnated in
the world of my favorite
dating sim where I'm in
love with the villainess,
Claire Francois.
How could anyone not fall for that wicked
gaggle she does when
she's being malicious?
She's my perfect evil queen
and I would die for her.
Let's see which of us performs
better on tomorrow's exams.
If my scores are higher, then you're to
remove yourself from this academy at once.
And finally, we have the results
of the Magic Ability Exam.
First place, Ray Taylor. Unmeasurable?
What does unmeasurable even mean?
And she's still placed first?
It wasn't even close then?
All right, everyone.
That's enough chatter.
Now then,
because we've not yet determined how
to categorize Ray Taylor's scores,
and because she is a new student,
she has been excluded
from the overall results.
That is all. Dismissed.
Ray, how did you...
I demand an explanation for this at once!
Unmeasurable magic ability!
I have never heard of such a thing!
Ray, did you intentionally miss the
target during the magic tool exam?
Wait, miss it on purpose?
Why would she do that?
Not sure.
That's why I asked.
You missed it, and you
still came in first?
Which means her score in the Magic
Ability Exam must have been quite high.
Higher than what is accurately measurable.
If that's true, it stands to reason
her marks were above exceptional.
Nah,
that would have caused the
scoring device to malfunction,
which leaves us with just
one possible explanation.
Earth and water, fire, wind.
There are four elemental attributes, and
normally a person can possess only one.
But what if Rey here
actually has two of them?
That's absurd!
A commoner like her?
No, she could never have
been granted such a gift.
Well, it's merely my own
speculation, of course.
But if you are right, then...
Rey's a dual caster.
Ding, ding, ding!
We have a winner!
The protagonist of Revolution
can use two attributes.
Earth and water.
As Misha deduced,
she's a dual caster, an incredibly rare
classification in the world of the game.
What's more, she's ranked
exceptional in both elements.
The highest score you can get.
That triggers the unmeasurable result,
which we just saw play out
in the first exam event.
So yeah, long story short, it
was totally rigged in my favor.
You did great.
Placing third behind two of the
princesses is an amazing achievement.
Yes, she's right.
You really needn't trouble
yourself over some commoner.
True.
I'll put her out of my mind at once.
Oh, hello, Claire!
My goodness, are you okay?
You look like you saw a ghost.
Oh, do I?
Well, perhaps you shouldn't
appear as if from nowhere!
What do you want, commoner?
You were excluded from the exam
results, so our competition is canceled.
But we were only betting
that you would win.
Since you didn't, I get a favor.
What?
I made sure to choose my
words extremely carefully.
But if you don't win, that means I do.
And you'll have to do one
thing that I ask of you.
My score wasn't counted,
so yours can't be higher.
That means I automatically
win the bet because
we never said that I had
to do better than you.
You brazen little cheater!
Yeah, sorry to trick you.
If you blatantly deceive me,
the results are nullified!
I have no obligation to you!
Wait, what?
You're gonna go back on your word?
After we swore in front of God?
In this kingdom, swearing to God
is an act of extreme significance.
Anyone who breaks that vow is held in
contempt regardless of social status.
What is it that you demand?
So you are gonna do it?
Sure is good to love an honest woman.
Hurry up and tell me what you want!
My request is a simple one.
Promise me you won't give up.
Huh?
No matter how bad things
get, you can't give up.
You have to fight through
whatever comes till the very end.
Wait, I'm confused.
That's all you want of me?
A promise that I won't give up?
Yep.
Say it and I'll consider your debt paid.
I must admit I thought you
would ask for something dodgier.
I totes can if that's what you prefer.
You want to fulfill some
hot fantasies I have?
That's quite all right!
Very well, fair is fair.
I swear before God that I,
Claire, will never give up!
No matter what happens,
I will not abandon hope.
And I promise to continue
fighting until the end.
Have I fulfilled our
verbal agreements then?
Yes, you have.
Thank you
I won't lose again
Oh, Ms. Claire!
What do you want now? I love you!
Well, I honestly despise you, Retailer!
One, two, one, say not to you?
All I want, only you.
Don't know if you're in love with me?
You're in love with me, right?
I want you to say not to you.
Happy End.
You're in love with me.
I call you who, I call you who.
Hey, you're in love with me.
If you don't like it, I don't
think it's going to start.
So raise your hand! I'm right now.
The love of happiness is just one thing.
From the heart of the heart.
Raise your hand!
Once again, let your
hands be a good world.
I don't want to give up until I miss you!
It's interesting, I love you.
It's been quite the process, but
I made it to the final interview.
Kapow!
I'm in the scholarship program at the
Academy, so I don't have to pay tuition.
But I'd like another source
of income for basic living.
Also, if I have a job as your maid,
I get to make some extra cash while
spending quality time with you,
which is a total win-win sitch.
Win-win sitch.
It can't be a win-win if
there are no mutual benefits!
Reject it!
Shred that application!
If you're absolutely certain
that's what you want, Miss Claire.
However, I found her to be
superior to every other candidate.
Her skills are exceptional.
She also appears to have
a deep sense of loyalty.
I have to disagree with you.
Loyalty's for the puppies.
Ladies, what you see is...
True love!
True love.
I simply cannot have a maid working
for me who says things like that!
I heard shouting.
Is everything all right?
This is Claire's father, Dole, a duke
and the kingdom's minister of finance.
He's also third in the line of succession
behind the king and prime minister.
I apologize for the disturbance, sir.
We were selecting a maid to
attend school with Miss Claire,
and it would appear she is not happy
with my top choice for the position.
Her personality renders
her completely unsuitable.
She's always attempting
to make a fool of me.
Oh?
If our headmaid has chosen her, I'm
sure she is more than qualified.
But, if Claire disapproves of this
decision, then we will not hire her.
Thank you, Father.
I am confident there are many
others suited to be your maid.
Please wait, Your Grace.
I hope you will pardon my insolence, but
I would like to have a word with you.
Are you a commoner requesting
to speak to a noble?
It appears my Claire's judgment
of your character was correct.
Such impudence will not be.
Irvine Manuel.
And just who might that be?
March the 3rd.
Five hundred thousand gold.
Father, what does that mean?
Would you two mind giving me a
moment to converse with the girl?
Might I assign a guard first?
Consider it an order.
Must we both leave?
Surely at least I can stay.
I am sorry, Claire.
Bear with me for now. I'll be back.
I simply need to confirm a few things.
Of course.
Now then, why don't you
tell me who you are?
And what exactly you know?
Father!
It's settled.
You will accept this girl as your maid.
What did she say to you?
You were against the
idea only a moment ago.
All you need to know is that she is
trustworthy and qualified to be your maid.
You rat!
Tell me what you said
to my father right now!
Nothing you don't know.
I just told him I love
you and always will.
No!
This is completely absurd!
Please think of what this request entails.
You hear the way she speaks to me.
How can I trust her when I'm a - Enough.
It's easy to find someone
obedient to serve at your side,
but I want the only child of Francois to
prove she knows how to rein in a servant.
Are you truly insisting I
hire this crass commoner?
I am.
Very well, then.
You As my maid you are to obey me.
Under no circumstances
will I tolerate slacking.
Understood.
Yes.
Then you shall start tomorrow.
I'm so looking forward to it.
She's in the best hands.
I'll spend my whole life servicing her.
Again I do not care for your phrasing.
I love you Miss Claire.
I'll see you tomorrow.
What did I do to deserve this?
I can't endure this a moment more!
You lech!
You believe your eyes
won't expose your thoughts?
My apologies, miss.
I just need a few more minutes
of staring at that I'll be done.
Absolutely not!
Turn around at once!
Please, Ms.
Clay!
What exactly are you staring at?
All right, Ray, deep breaths.
It isn't very nice to tease
Miss Claire like that, you know.
Yeah, you're right.
I'm sorry.
She just looked so radiant
I couldn't help myself.
That's enough of your revolting flattery!
So ridiculous.
Nothing good will ever come of
entrusting anything to this commoner.
I'll have Lene assist me
with changing as always.
Now, Miss Claire, give her a chance.
If you don't allow Ray to gain
any experience, she won't learn.
And that could really
lead to trouble later
if I get sick and can't take care of you.
Well, I suppose you have a point.
But still, this is Lene Oruso.
She's a senior maid who's been on Miss
Claire's staff since they were children.
She's actually from one of the wealthiest
merchant companies in the kingdom,
the Oruso Company.
Even though she's a commoner, she's pretty
well off and isn't hurting for money.
In fact,
the Oruso Company only sent
her to serve the Minister of
Finance in order to establish
a business connection with him.
But more on that later.
All right, I'm finished.
Are you certain, Ms.
Claire?
You've left your peppers again.
It's uncouth to be so wasteful.
Sometimes she seems more like
an older sister than a maid.
What does it matter, Lene?
I eat plenty of other vegetables.
Yes, I'm aware.
But this is the only crop that was
paid for with the common folk's taxes.
It's a sign of gratitude
if a noble eats them.
But I'm...
You're them to me!
I'd be honored to eat them!
It's like kissing you in direct!
There, I ate them!
It worked. Nice job.
Just happy to be of assistance.
Yes, I've no doubt my nutritional
intake is your utmost concern.
Now then, who can tell us about the
effects of Cooley III's policies?
What about you, Miss Claire?
Yes, sir.
As a maid, Lene doesn't come
to lectures with Miss Claire.
However,
since I'm also a student, I get to serve
in her place whenever we're at school.
And thus, our kingdom
became self-sufficient.
We no longer needed to
rely on imports for food.
Very good answer. Thank you.
Hey there, Ray. Huh?
Oh, hi, Prince Rod.
Got some time?
Why don't we play a game together?
Oh gosh, I wish I could, but
I've got maid stuff to do.
Is that so?
Guess I'll just have to ask again later.
I'm here whenever you're ready.
Thanks, but I really need
to take care of Miss Claire.
Bring Claire along with you.
We can all have fun.
I totally get I'm in a dating sim,
but the amount of flirt bombs going off
at all times still makes me super anxious.
Anyone who wants to follow
Prince Rod's route has to
get excellent scores on
pretty much all of the exams.
At least that's what I thought,
but apparently just throwing the
magic tool exam wasn't enough.
I just hope it doesn't get awkward.
Hey, Thane, you want to join in?
Usually I select Prince
Thane's route because
that's the one where Miss Claire
shows up the most. Leave me be.
Oh, crap.
That was the sound of Prince Thane's
affection for me crashing to the floor.
Uh, Ray, why are you crying?
Because I don't want you to
follow me, but here you are.
hi ray first catch your breath then tell
me how class went no trouble to report
but i really can't say
i did any actual work
though that's because
miss claire's always been
an excellent student it
sounds like i won't be
doing a lot as her tutor
then will i oh don't
you worry i promise we'll
keep you much busier
in the afternoons now
let's get out there and do
everything we can to keep
our mistress happy oh
miss claire i've been
meaning to ask if you've
heard about the latest
confection by brumet more
than heard of it i've
had a taste in fact they
call it chocolate and it's heavenly really
you're so lucky brumet is
the most popular eatery
in the capital that you've
already sampled their
much awaited new item
i have it's very sweet
and creamy with a hint
of bitterness it has a
rich aroma and tastes
unlike any other sweet i've
Never know.
If you're interested in trying it, I
can have some sent to your room later.
What?
You'd do that for me? Hey!
No fair! I want some too!
Commoner, run along and prepare
some chocolate for Pepi and Loretta.
My pleasure, Miss Claire.
Miss Claire, are you sure it's okay
to keep someone like her by your side?
Alas, I have no choice.
I said I didn't want her anywhere near me.
But father felt it was important for
me to practice taming the servants.
Which means I won't be allowed
even a moment to myself.
That must be so terrible for you.
You're the one I'm
complaining about, Simpleton.
You're so lucky to serve, Miss Claire.
Though I don't imagine
you've tried the chocolate.
Unless she gives you treats
when you've been a good girl.
Treats, don't be absurd.
There's no need to show
compassion to a maid like her.
That's completely true.
I don't need her to give me sweets.
Just one freshly worn blouse of hers
can carry me for three whole meals.
You hear that?
This sort of thing is exactly
what makes her so repellent.
You certainly do like Miss Claire
a great deal, don't you? Oh, no.
I don't like her.
Huh?
Was that sadness I just saw crawl
across your face, Miss Claire?
It would bother you if I
stopped loving you, wouldn't it?
Bother me?
It's your affection that bothers me!
You haven't stopped clinging to
Miss Claire since you arrived.
That's a blast, I was about to say.
I don't like Miss Claire.
I love her.
Truth be known, I'm
madly in love with her.
Now this is real luxury.
Indeed, it is far more
than a commoner deserves.
After all, the water of this spring
is drawn from the Thassel Volcano.
And is set to make your skin glow.
Oh, wow, God bless that volcano.
Come on, Miss Claire, let's go, Ray.
You'd better hurry and finish
up before you catch a cold.
All right, I'll go ahead and
give her skin a good scrubbing.
Do you think you could manage
washing her hair for me?
Yes, please!
If you try anything
funny, I will destroy you.
Well, you're quite good at this.
Thank you very much.
Your hair is so beautiful
and so easy to wash.
I love the feel of naturally
straight hair, don't you?
One of Lene's tasks is to do
Miss Claire's hair every morning.
She's the artist behind
those gorgeous curls.
The style was actually inspired
by Miss Claire's mother's hair.
Okay, I'm going to rinse it off now.
Absolutely not with the nosebleeds!
I smeared my lipstick!
This has been wonderful.
You really are quite talented, Ray.
I consider it a privilege
to get to work with you.
Really?
I would suggest holding
off on celebrating her.
Something tells me this commoner
won't be around for long.
Aw, stop being so hard on her.
At least use her name instead of commoner.
A commoner is a commoner.
Perhaps if you stop telling
everyone you're in love with me,
I might refer to you by name
instead of sad generic nouns.
No thanks!
Don't answer right away!
You really are a strange girl, aren't you?
I know you've only
recently met Miss Claire,
yet it seems as though you know
nearly everything about her.
Chalk it up to the power of love.
Well then, good night.
I'll be heading back to the
servant's quarters if you need me.
Okay.
Good night, sweet dreams.
You alright, Ms.
Claire?
Did the heat make you dizzy?
A little.
Seemed like you were sort of in
a daze when we were in the bath.
What if my fingers are magic?
Have I possessed your mind?
Silence, you!
Shouldn't you be going back
to your room about now?
I will, once you're able to sleep.
Want a goodnight kiss to help you relax?
Maids are not permitted to do
that under any circumstances!
I know, I just wanted to say it.
Honestly, commoner, grow up.
Are you still here?
I am.
I see.
Then explain something to me.
Why do you keep telling me you love me?
I just think you're so adorable.
I can't help myself sometimes.
So you're fixated on my appearance.
No, I love your personality too.
I am well aware of what
kind of personality I have.
And I know that it is
not the lovable kind.
That's not true at all.
Spare me your hollow flattery.
Tell me the truth.
What exactly is it you want from me?
Listen, Miss Claire.
I'm in love with you.
I'm here because I want to
be by your side. That's all.
I see you're not ready
to let go of that facade.
You really think I'm
making all this up? Yes.
Well then, it sounds like I'll have
to work harder to prove it to you.
Go to bed, you're impossible.
Good night, Miss Claire!
I'll see you tomorrow.
Have it your way.
I'll see you
next time.
I want that to be a part of the new world!
Let's do it!
I want to do it!
I want to do it.
Why?
Well, you're not going to die.
It's the end of the world!
I'm gonna teach you!
Miss Claire, do you like games?
Who do you think I am?
As the only Francois daughter,
I know every form of amusement
necessary in high society.
Oh, great!
Then would you like to play
the Prince game with me?
Huh?
What in the world is that?